The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives a magicless boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the next wizard king.
Though Asta's situation is practically unheard of,
there are others residing in this kingdom
who possess at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely use spells at all.
They make up a very small minority,
living their lives in the shadows.
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
It's a dream.
Ah...
So... Is that a no, then?
Are you sure? No...
I'm sorry, I can't hear you. Could you repeat that?
I said, are you sure I'm good enough for you?
What? Don't be silly.
Dazu, I love you.
And I want you to become my wife one day.
Excellent work, Dazu!
Hello, ma'am.
You don't use any magic.
And yet somehow you do just as much as everyone else does.
Huh?
I know.
There's so many graves here, you can't count them all.
Wonder how many popped up after the big attack.
Huh?
Um, hello, miss.
Pardon me.
Would you mind if I asked you a question?
Sure, that's alright.
Have you seen this little girl?
We're also trying to find a beautiful young lady with a pair of horns on her head.
I can't count them all.
Horns?
the big attack um hello miss pardon me would you mind if I asked you a question
sure that's all right have you seen this little girl we're also trying to find a
beautiful young lady with a pair of horns on her head
Lawrence I'm sorry I don't understand no dice this might ring a bell you know
anything about a group that's got a grudge against devils I would assume
everyone has something against devils you know about the one that caused all the
destruction here don't you yeah I do judging by your cloaks I take it your
magic Knights we are I lost my husband in that attack and his mother why didn't
any of you show up to help us our numbers were stretched way too thin the whole
kingdom was in chaos I'm sorry because we weren't here your loved ones died
excuse me
that cross and that silver hair are they silvas what are a couple of royals doing out here I cut it
out stop staring I have a question does this girl look familiar to you I don't think so cute kid
though we're here looking for her and another girl who has horns on her head please let us know if you
see them anywhere hang on did you see horns so you haven't seen them thanks no problem
excuse me sir have you seen this person no can't say that I have sorry but you didn't even look sorry
but I'm a little busy right now my house was just torn to pieces recently and no one came to help us
rebuild hey don't go let him what's wrong with them they're being indirect but it's obvious that the
people in this village are angry at the magic Knights for the way things were handled after what
happened to their home we can't blame them it's our job to protect the Clover Kingdom and we weren't
able to be here when they needed us the most you're right we failed them we won't get any useful
information by being forceful but narrow and Marie we have to save them I agree that time is of the
essence but panicking never produces results if you are a true magic Knight then you'll learn how to
keep a level head right since questioning people isn't working perhaps we should try something else okay
Marie what is wrong with you
I guess you're not Marie you'd better stay away from my daughter excuse me I'm a little tense here
as the other half of the double G duo it's my job to back him up how about a nice treat from your new
friends
I said don't touch my little girl or I'll kill you both
you should probably look a bit more closely next time
I don't need advice from you if I even think it might be Marie then I'm running straight over to save
her damn it Marie where did they take you I'll find you angel please wait for me let's try not to
attract more attention to ourselves okay did you call me wait what I could have sworn I heard you shout
my name on top of that you call me an angel but I don't think I've ever been called that even when
I was a spring chicken what the hell are you yapping about you crone I'm sorry ma'am but what is your
name it's Maggie but angels fine too didn't you hear us we said Marie well that's different just a little
did something go wrong Dazoo yes we'll talk down there
Dazoo welcome back you did well thank you everyone how much longer do we plan to keep hiding in this
cellar I think it's better to go ahead and execute these two it seems we have an
even bigger problem on our hands now the magic Knights have just arrived what did they track our
location no they couldn't have master cobwe's transparency magic is concealing our presence
completely but they still might have planted something ahead of time transparency
magic detection decoder that must be it what the hell that thing tracks people were possessed by
devils how did it get here I can't believe they pulled a stunt like this wait not yet I have an idea
please tell me you guys got some good info no unfortunately the townspeople weren't being very
cooperative we tried to figure out where their hideout might be but no luck as of yet and despite
my best efforts to track their mana we still can't pinpoint the target look at this
the signal still seems pretty unstable it's also troubling that we don't know how much time we have
left before they notice that magic item if we don't find them before that happens things could get
worse well what'd you learn we mostly just talked to an elderly woman she was an interesting person so
basically nothing got it look I'm not here to screw around I'll do whatever it takes to hunt down those
monsters who took my sister once I get my hands on them it's over what's wrong rich boy they're on
the move yeah where you think they know we're on to them I don't know but something real weird's going
on I'm sure they realize by now that magic Knights are in the area perhaps they're creating some type of
diversion all right then I think Gordon and I ought to take another quick look around the town I'll let
you guys borrow my wheels for a while thank you that'll make it easier to get back even Captain
Nozel's using me as a chauffeur get on and hurry that worked like a charm hopefully it'll buy us a
little extra time I can't believe we have to contend with them when the eye of the midnight Sun ransacked
our kingdom many of the magic Knights were directly involved in the chaos that ensued possessed or not
they should have been held responsible I couldn't agree with you more and yet all they're doing right
now is trying to protect each other they're a joke we obviously don't mean a thing to them it is our
responsibility to show them what the true meaning of justice is yes that's right we have to stand up for
the people of this kingdom and make sure anyone who threatens them is severely punished now I say
the first step to exacting justice is to execute these two servants of the devil I agree then we can
put their corpses on display as a symbol of negligence arrogance and deceit that the magic Knights
displayed when we needed their assistance they showed their true colors when they sided with the
devil and now they must be stopped exactly from this day forward the devil banishers will be the
ones to keep the clover kingdom safe perhaps it's better if we hold off on the executions for now how
can you possibly believe that's better I feel just as strongly as you I can't forgive anyone who
communes with the devil but if we hang on to them for a little longer we may be able to lure out
Asta the boy who's possessed if we killed all three at the same time we could make an even stronger
case for master cowboy's cause that's a good point if we use these two as bait the black bulls are sure
to act Asta's possessed he's the one we really want that makes sense after all he's practically a devil
himself we can't hope to bring justice to the clover kingdom until that monstrous villain is dead
yes I'm glad you agree so now we should determine the best way to capture him let me think here
they've stopped moving no one's around let's check in there
Marie we're here for you just tell me where you are
well great they deceived us that was the only lead we had how are we supposed to find them now
damn it we need a new plan let's regroup with Yami and Gordon and head back to the capital
we'll be all right you really think this will work we made it through that night and our luck hasn't
run out since then all thanks to you bow it isn't just me if I hadn't met you I wouldn't have any
purpose right now I'd just be wandering aimlessly through my life and if not for you I would have
felt nothing but despair after being left alone to suffer in this world you give me hope does it I
believe in you with all my heart if you're by my side I'm sure everything will be fine
what's going on where am I so you're awake this is a break room inside the palace is that you Owen
oh yeah narrow hold on don't leave
don't you think you ought to find out what's happening before you hightail it out of here kid
I was able to rid your body of the drug so you should be fine now thanks a lot doc let me get
this straight narrow and Marie were kidnapped by a group called the devil panickers it's banishers
genius and if things had gone differently they would have taken you too yeah I heard that you
saved my life in the nick of time you're the best Noelle well it's not like I saved you because I care
about you or anything I just didn't want to let them get away with whatever they were doing I wish I
could have stopped them from kidnapping narrow that's not your fault though if I had just been a little bit
stronger I know it hurts but there's no use in crying over spilled milk now Owen says you're
healthy enough to leave so why don't you guys head to the hideout no I'm gonna go out there and look
for those two did you not hear anything I just said are you really that stupid we don't have any clues as
to where they took them which means all you'd be doing is running around on a wild goose chase
well good luck everybody what are you gonna do captain yummy sometimes a captain's gotta tend to
his business you know oh yeah I already talked to Ghosh about this but if he freaks out don't be afraid
to rough him up some try not to kill him all right that sound fair yeah I guess so it looks like
everyone's here the golden dawn and aqua deer are guarding the borders and the coral peacocks and
purple orcas have some important restoration work to attend to we certainly shouldn't expect them to
walk away from those responsibilities right now so hopefully we'll be able to take care of this
matter with only the people we have present if it's all right I have something to say first it's a
distinct possibility that my subordinates are the ones who orchestrated this whole scheme therefore I'm
willing to provide you with any information you require thank you for your cooperation as of right
now our top priority should be rescuing the two people who were kidnapped we can delay the punishments
at the moment it'd be helpful if you could share some background on your team yes a good idea well
then chairman Dom Natio please tell us everything you can this is Kabwe Karion he's 38 years of age his
transparency magic allows him to make himself and the people around him disappear he can't hide his
mana so he doesn't have the same skill as the former purple orca's captain besides him there's a man
named Onobi Shinho 31 years old his barrier magic creates a barricade whose radius is about five times his
height the structure promptly explodes if anyone tries to tear it down third there's Siona Caverly 29 years old
Siona is a paper magic user meaning she's able to control any thickness or length of paper at will
I could slice up all three easy peasy we shouldn't do anything to them until we know for sure that
they're involved with the devil banishers once there's proof you can slice and dice as much as
you want but for now we need to put our heads together and find those two girls you got it
beanpole it's also important to note that the black bull happens to be a wielder of arcane stage magic
that makes her essential to our strategy for defeating the devil we cannot afford to lose
her at any cost they're both important the other girls part of our kingdom as well so it's imperative
that we bring her back unharmed hey it was a pretty good speech prickly princess you're a lot smarter
than that stick bug over there you shut it yummy complimented me wait no now's not the time to be
giddy about that even if it was an ambush it's hard to believe Asta was overpowered by someone who's not
a fighter they use something he's never dealt with before apparently the assailant subdued him with a
sleeping potion are you kidding me that's what I call a dirty underhanded trick the kids had training
so he can negate just about any spell someone throws at him and of course he can handle a physical attack
no problem up until now he's basically only had to fight people in a way he understands which is face
to face clearly this group has quite a gifted strategist in their ranks let's not forget they
also managed to use our own magic item against us if these guys are going around calling themselves
devil banishers then it's probably safe to say that they're trying to get rid of devils right
yes then why haven't they off their hostages yet it's not like they haven't had a chance
provided that my subordinates are the responsible party in this matter
out of those three Cobway is the one with the most enduring sense of justice and after the incident
with the eye of the midnight sun his hatred of devils became even more intense
in fact Cobway was extremely displeased when the execution of the devil possessed was
postponed then why not kill them even quicker if it were me I would have skipped right past the
sleeping potions and slaughtered them all I'm sure they had their reasons stupid ones assuming Cobway's
in charge I'm certain that he would prefer a proper execution to murdering them on site most likely he
will attempt to take their lives in front of the biggest audience he can he hopes to gain the public's
approval which will help him to justify taking the law into his own hands like some kind of vigilante
if I know my subordinates this is the method they'll probably use yeah hell of a team you've got there
pal fortunately if your assumptions are accurate it stands to reason that both of the hostages are
still alive good but if there was a public execution there would likely be a few citizens who were in
favor of it as I've seen firsthand many people are resentful of the kingdom's decision-making since
the eye of the midnight Sun attacked us the wounds from that incident have yet to be healed that devil
committed unspeakable acts and our people are still reeling from the shock of it if we don't correct this
quickly we might just find ourselves dealing with a large-scale rebellion right now we're preparing
to face a threat from outside the last thing we need is an additional conflict inside we have to
nip this in the bud before it becomes uncontrollable if they do decide to go through with this public
execution then they won't be able to do it without us knowing question is what do we do when the time
comes well I trust you'll all proceed with caution yes I wish I could give you better instruction but
I don't know what else to say I can't help feeling we're missing an important piece of the puzzle somehow
花魂に転んで傷ついて気づけば誰ももうどこにもいない
かかわいい
の
remember
I'll be the one executing them!
Execution? There's no way I'll let that happen!
If those psychos hurt Maria or even make her cry, I'll be the one executing them!
Black Clover? There's no way I'll let that happen!
Black Clover, page 145. Rescue. Hold on, Angel! Big Brother's coming to get you!